Keroles Nabil Saad

full stack developer .NET

https://github.com/kerolesnabil2050

PROFILE

Acquiring a challenging vacancy, related to my education and experience within a dynamic organization enabling me to utilize my capabilities to the maximum and enrich my knowledge & practical experience which will make a positive contribution to the organization.

EDUCATION

Information Technology Institute (ITI) student scholarship Professional Web	10/2022 – 06/2023
Development and BI	Assiut, Egypt
Minya University faculty of computer science department Bioinformatics A senior student by cumulative GPA of 3.22	10/2018 – 07/2022 Minya, Egypt

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trained at Information Technology Institute. Gaining essential knowledge of embedded systems design and programming.	07/2021 – 09/2021 Minya, Egypt
Cashier at Bassem market - Ensuring high levels of customers satisfaction through excellent service	06/2020 – 10/2020 North Coast, Egypt

	- (6) F
PROJECTS	
Graduation Project: Saving Live MySQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Java Script, Jquery, Bootstrap	11/2021 - 06/2022
Supermarket System Supermarket using c#, entity framework , linq , wpf, SQL	01/2023 - 02/2023
E-commerce clothes Web site E-commerce clothes Web site using Asp.net , mvc, signal R,design patterns, Ajax, JavaScript, Bootstrap, sql , HTML, CSS	03/2023 - 04/2023
Linkedin web site Linkedin web site using Asp.net ,Web API, angular, Design Patterns, OOP, SQL	04/2023 - 05/2023

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Design Patterns • Linq • OOP • C#	
• Design Patterns • Ling • OOP • C#	
• Asp.net core web Api • Entity framework • Asp.net core MVC • SQL Server	

LANGUAGES

English	Arabic
very good at speaking, listening and writing.	Mother tongue.

PERSONAL SKILLS

_ 1	
Anal	マオキャクコー
Allai	ytical

Handles Stress.

Problem Solver

Flexible